{
   "response_code":0,
   "results":[
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"French is an official language in Canada.",
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "False"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "False"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "False"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "False"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "False"
         ]
      }
   ]
}